Guide to the Red Hot Organization Archive, 1989-2004 MSS.191
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XIX: General Red Hot Organization
  - Subseries A: Administration Files, American Express folders contain account information. Same for Checks, Cheque books, Deposits, Monthly accounting statements, Padell Nadell etc, Martin Greene Ravden folders, Bank statement folders, Information Document Request folders
    - IRS - Information for Application for Recognition of Exemption, 1993-1995; cuid8229 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - June 93 - June 94 account, 1994-1995; cuid8230 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Kaktus Valley, 1991-1992; cuid8231 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - King Cole Inc. - Entity information, 2002; cuid8232 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - King Cole Inc. - Incorporation, 1990-1991; cuid8233 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Landauer, Tracy (Balber Pickard Battistoni Maldonado & Van Der Tuin, PC), 2001-2002; cuid8234 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Lawyers Alliance for New York, 1993-2001; cuid8235 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Leases, 1990-1997; cuid8236 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Ledgers, 2000, 2002; cuid8237 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - License requests, 1991-2001; cuid8238 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - List of gay periodicals, [n.d.]; cuid8239 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Lounge $$$, 1998-2000; cuid8240 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Lounge - paid bills (Restricted), 1998; cuid8241 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Martin Greene Ravden - Company correspondence, 1992; cuid8242 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Martin Greene Ravden - UK correspondence, 1994; cuid8243 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Martin Greene Ravden - USA correspondence with UK re: 6/30/94, 1994-1995; cuid8244 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Memos, 1992; cuid8245 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Messengers, 1994-1995; cuid8246 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Minolta Business Systems, Inc. Maintenance Supply Agreements; CBS Whitcom Purchase Agreement, 1996-1997; cuid8247 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous literature, [n.d.]; cuid8248 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Money Market bank statements, 1996-2000; cuid8249 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      Includes deposit tickets, statements, transfer requests, grant awardees' information and more.
    - Monthly accounting statements, 1992-1993; cuid8250 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Monthly accounting statements, 1994-1996; cuid8251 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Morrissey "England's Answer to the H-Bomb", 1991; cuid8252 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - MTV, 1998 - 1999; cuid8253 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Native Tongues, 1991 - 1993; cuid8254 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Notes on operation of PAYE re: payments to casual and freelance staff in the Film Industry, 1990 - 1991; cuid8255 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Opening Entries Report, 1999; cuid8256 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Oppenheimer & Co., Inc., 1996-1999; cuid8257 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Organization cashflow, 1992; cuid8258 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Outlicensing, 1992 - 1999; cuid8259 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), 1996; cuid8260 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), 1996-1997; cuid8261 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), 1996-1997; cuid8262 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), 1997-1998; cuid8263 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), June - Sep 1998; cuid8264 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting) (Restricted), Oct - Nov 1998; cuid8265 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting) (Restricted), Feb - June 1999; cuid8266 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), Dec 1998 - Feb 1999; cuid8267 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), Mar - May 1999; cuid8268 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), June - Sep 1999; cuid8269 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), Oct - Dec 1999; cuid8270 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting) (Restricted), 2000-2001; cuid8271 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting) (Restricted), 2002; cuid8272 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company - reports, 1998; cuid8273 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Payroll / Taxes (Restricted), 1995; cuid8274 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Payroll - Unofficial file, "Francine's" (Restricted), 1995; cuid8275 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Payroll (Restricted), 1998; cuid8276 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Payroll (Restricted), 1999-2001; cuid8277 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Permanent file, 1992-1994; cuid8278 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      Includes press packets, information on grants awarded, organization structures, legal forms.
    - PolyGram Holding, Inc. - Back end advance, 1998; cuid8279 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Posting reports - Republic National Bank/HSBC Bank, 2000; cuid8280 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Posting reports - Republic National Bank/HSBC Bank, 2001; cuid8281 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Posting reports - Signature Bank, 2001 - 2002; cuid8282 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Proposal (film), [n.d.]; cuid8283 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Ralph Lauren promotional CDs, 1997; cuid8284 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Receipts - Reimbursed (Restricted), 1993-1995; cuid8285 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Red Hot + Bothered / * Important Beat stills, 1994-1995; cuid8286 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      Content
      Apparently includes files on Beat Experience, America Is Dying Slowly and Red Hot + Bothered.
    - Red Hot #15, 1990-1996; cuid8287 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      Includes files on Red Hot + Blue, Red Hot + Dance, No Alternative, Red Hot + Country, Red Hot + Cool, Beat Experience.
    - Red Hot AIDS Charitable Trust/London office, 1993-1995; cuid8288 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Red Hot Disk 1, 1989-1996; cuid8289 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Red Hot Minis, 1990-1996; cuid8290 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Royalty statement - "We're All in This Together: A Benefit for AIDS", 1994; cuid8291 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Sebastian, Earle, [n.d.]; cuid8292 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Share certificate of John Carlin, 1994 - 1995; cuid8293 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Slogans, [n.d.]; cuid8294 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Statement of income and expenses, 1994; cuid8295 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Storage item list, 2006; cuid8296 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Strauss, Seymour (Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company), 1997 - 2003; cuid8297 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Summary of cash balances and related schedules of cash receipts and disbursements, 1994; cuid8298 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Summary of cash balances and related schedules of cash receipts and disbursements, 1995; cuid8299 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Summary of cash balances and related schedules of cash receipts and disbursements, 1996; cuid8300 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Tax audit 12/31/94 (Restricted), 1994 - 1997; cuid8301 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Tax audit 12/31/94 - "Our take" (Restricted), 1993 - 1995; cuid8302 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Tax forms (Restricted), 1990 - 1996; cuid8303 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Tax return filing instructions, prepared by Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Co., 1998; cuid8304 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Taxes - Foreign, 1996; cuid8305 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Trademarks, 1994-1999; cuid8306 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - UK Liquidation, 1995 - 1996; cuid8307 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - UK office: Correspondence, 1996; cuid8308 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Video tracking log: Misc., [n.d.]; cuid8309 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - W.A.D. Party '02, 2002; cuid8310 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Wire transfer requests/confirmations - Signature Bank (Restricted), 2001; cuid8311 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Women's Moves, [n.d.]; cuid8312 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Womyn for Womyn: a lesbian resource centre, [n.d.]; cuid8313 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - WTC Business Recovery Grant, 2002-2003; cuid8314 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Zoo TV, 1993; cuid8315 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Art Against AIDS - On The Road, c.a. 1989; cuid8316 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Envelopes - Downtown Arts Festival, [n.d.]; cuid8317 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Happy New Year from Red Hot Organization, c.a. 1994; cuid8318 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Information packet, c.a. 1993; cuid8319 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Invitations to "the heart of summer", [n.d.]; cuid8320 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Invitations to a party to honor The Red Hot Organization, 1995; cuid8321 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Postcards - Designs by David McDiarmid, commissioned by AIDS Council of NSW, (ACON) Australia, c.a. 1992; cuid8322 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Postcards - Levi's Presents: A Month of Music, [n.d.]; cuid8323 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Press clippings - The Condom Project, cuid8324 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Press clippings - General, 1993-1998; cuid8325 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Press clippings - General, 1994-2001; cuid8326 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Press clippings - Love in the 90's, 1995 - 1998; cuid8327 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Press clippings - Miscellaneous, 1991 - 1996; cuid8328 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Press clippings - Museums: New York, 1995-1996; cuid8329 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Press clippings - 10th Anniversary, 2000 - 2001; cuid8330 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Press clippings - Twentieth-Century Blues: The Songs of Noel Coward, 1998; cuid8331 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Press masters, [n.d.]; cuid8332 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Press master samples, c.a. 1998; cuid8333 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Press release - 10th Anniversary, cuid8334 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Red Hot Again Photography Auction catalogue, 1991; cuid8335 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Season's Greetings card, [n.d.]; cuid8336 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Stickers - Red Hot Organization, [n.d.]; cuid8337 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Stickers - True Love (in association with The Condom Project), cuid8338 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material
    - Negatives: "[Suite] pictures Mark Valentine", [n.d.]; cuid8339 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - All Access: The Horde Festival CD-ROM, 1996; cuid8341 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Red Hot & Skin; PonyCanyon Entertainment (Singapore), 1993; cuid8342 (Box 29, Folder 35)
      Double audio compact disc
    - We're All in This Together; GRP Records, 1993; cuid8343 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Subseries E: Awards
    - VH1 Honors, 1995; cuid8344 (Box 29, Folder 37)
- Oversize Series I: Red Hot + Blue, 1990
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 1990
    - Posters - Red Hot + Blue, [n.d.]; cuid8345 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings, 1990 - 1991; cuid8346 (Box [46])
    - Promotional single: "Night and Day," U2; Island Records Ltd., 1990; cuid8347 (Box 42)
      Sound Disc: Analog, 45 rpm; 12 in.
    - T-shirt order form, [n.d.]; cuid8348 (Box [46])
  - Subseries B: Red Hot + Dance
    - Red Hot + Dance - 2 inch Quad Master One, December 15, 1991; ID: 191.0155A (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0155A)
      Format: 2 inch Quad
      TRT: Unknown
    - Red Hot + Dance - Master One - Recording Notes, 1991; cuid8349 (Box TBA, Folder ID: 191.0155B)
    - Red Hot + Dance - 2 inch Quad Master Two, December 15, 1991; ID: 191.0156A (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0156A)
    - Red Hot + Dance - Master Two - Recording Notes, 1991; cuid8350 (Box TBA, Folder ID: 191.0156B)
    - Red Hot + Dance - 2 inch Quad Master Three, December 15, 1991; ID: 191.0157A (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0157A)
    - Red Hot + Dance - Master Three - Recording Notes, 1991; cuid8351 (Box TBA, Folder ID: 191.0157B)
    - Urge Overkill - Take A Walk - 1/4 inch Open Reel, November 2, 1993; ID: 191.0158 (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0158)
      Format: 1/4 inch Open Reel
      TRT: [4 mins 36 secs]
    - Matthew Sweet - Super Deformed - 1/4 inch Open Reel, October 21, 1993; ID: 191.0159 (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0159)
      TRT: [3 mins 55 secs]
    - Urge Overkill - Take A Walk - 1/4 inch Open Reel, November 2, 1993; ID: 191.0160 (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0160)
    - Red Hot + Dance - Miscellaneous Paperwork, Folder One, [1991-1993]; cuid8352 (Box TBA, Folder data_value_missing_a2db954e4570bca2fac505d841807af9)
    - Red Hot + Dance - Miscellaneous Paperwork, Folder Two, [1991-1993]; cuid8353 (Box TBA, Folder data_value_missing_86e10f27e0dfb1c14057dd8d6b8867b4)
    - Red Hot + Dance - AIDS Dancathon - 2 inch Quad, Reel 1 of 5, November 30, 1991; ID: 191.0161 (Box 61, Media ID: 191.0161)
    - Red Hot + Dance - AIDS Dancathon - 2 inch Quad, Reel 2 of 5, November 30, 1991; ID: 191.0162 (Box 61, Media ID: 191.0162)
    - Red Hot + Dance - AIDS Dancathon - 2 inch Quad, Reel 3 of 5, November 30, 1991; ID: 191.0163 (Box 61, Media ID: 191.0163)
    - Red Hot + Dance - AIDS Dancathon - 2 inch Quad, Reel 4 of 5, November 30, 1991; ID: 191.0164 (Box 61, Media ID: 191.0164)
    - Red Hot + Dance - AIDS Dancathon - 2 inch Quad, Reel 5 of 5, November 30, 1991; ID: 191.0165 (Box 61, Media ID: 191.0165)
      - Red Hot + Dance 9PP4 - 1/4 inch Open Reel, 1 of 2, Unknown; ID: 191.0166 (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0166)
    - Red Hot + Dance 9PP4 - 1/4 inch Open Reel, 2 of 2, Unknown; ID: 191.0167 (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0167)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Limited edition picture disc: "Well, Did You Evah!" by Deborah Harry & Iggy Pop; Chrysalis Records Ltd., 1990; cuid8354 (Box 42)
      Sound Disc: Analog; 12 in.
    - Red Hot + Blue, 1990; cuid8355 (Box 42)
      Laser disc
    - Single: "I've Got You Under My Skin," Neneh Cherry; Circa Records, 1990; cuid8356 (Box 42)
    - Sweatshirts - David Wojnarowicz artwork and text, c.a. 1990; cuid8357 (Box 30)
    - T-shirt - safe sex is hot sex, [n.d.]; cuid8358 (Box 31, Object ID: 191.2.0001)
- Oversize Series II: Red Hot + Dance
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Press clippings, 1991; cuid8359 (Box [46])
    - Promotional limited edition four record DJ box set; Epic Records, 1992; cuid8360 (Box 42)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Double A-Side: Crystal Waters / Sabrina Johnston - "Gypsy Woman" / "Peace;" Epic Records, 1992; cuid8361 (Box 42)
    - Red Hot + Dance double album; Columbia, 1992; cuid8362 (Box 42)
    - Remixes of "Too Funky," "Too Jazzy" and "Crazyman Dance," George Michael; Columbia, 1992; cuid8363 (Box 42)
      Sound Disc: Analog, 33 1/3 rpm; 12 in.
    - Single: "The Boy From Ipanema," Crystal Waters; verve Records, 1996; cuid8364 (Box 42)
      Sound disc: Analog, 33 1/3 rpm; 12 in.
    - T-shirt - Red Hot + Dance, 1993; cuid8365 (Box 31, Object ID: 191.2.0002)
    - T-shirts - safe sex is hot sex, male couple, [n.d.]; cuid8366 (Box 31, Object ID: 191.2.0003)
    - T-shirts - safe sex is hot sex, male couple close-up, [n.d.]; cuid8367 (Box 31, Object ID: 191.2.0004)
- Oversize Series V: Red Hot + Country
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - Helene Silverman (Restricted), 1993 - 1994; cuid8369 (Box [46])
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Posters - Red Hot + Country, [n.d.]; cuid8370 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings, 1994 - 1995; cuid8371 (Box [46])
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - T-shirts - Red Hot + Country, [n.d.]; cuid8372 (Box 32, Object ID: 191.2.0005)
    - T-shirts - Red Hot + Country, 1994; cuid8373 (Box 32, Object ID: 191.2.0006)
    - T-shirts - Red Hot + Country, 1994; cuid8374 (Box 32, Object ID: 191.2.0007)
- Oversize Series VI: Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Posters - Red Hot + Cool & Red Hot On Impulse, [n.d.]; cuid8375 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings, 1994; cuid8376 (Box [46])
    - Promotional sampler featuring "The Rubbers Song" by The Pharcyde and "Proceed II" by The Roots with Roy Ayers; Red Hot Organization, 1994; cuid8377 (Box 42)
    - Promotional sampler featuring special new mixes by The Roots and Da Beatminerz; Red Hot Organization, 1995; cuid8378 (Box 43)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material
    - Photographs: GRP publicity shots / Craftsmen photo, [n.d.]; cuid8379 (Box [46])
    - Photographs: Color + B&W, [n.d.]; cuid8380 (Box [46])
    - Photographs: Stolen Moments Color + B&W, [n.d.]; cuid8381 (Box [46])
    - Oversize Series VII: Red Hot + Bothered
      - Subseries B: Promotional Material
        - Posters - Red Hot + Bothered, 1995; cuid8382 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Subseries D: Merchandise
        - Red Hot + Bothered EP's with limited edition fanzines, Volume I Number 1; Red Hot Organization, 1995; cuid8383 (Box 44)
          Sound Disc: Analog, 33 1/3 rpm; 10 in.
        - Red Hot + Bothered EP's with limited edition fanzines, Volume I Number 2; Red Hot Organization, 1995; cuid8384 (Box 44)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Red Hot on Impulse double vinyl; GRP Records, 1994; cuid8385 (Box 43)
    - Single: "Proceed II," The Roots with Roy Ayers; Red Hot Organization, 1995; cuid8386 (Box 43)
    - Stolen Moments: Red Hot & Cool double vinyl; GRP Records, 1994; cuid8387 (Box 43)
      Sound Disc, Analog, 33 1/3 rpm; 12 in.
- Oversize Series VII: Red Hot + Bothered, [n.d.]
  - Subseries B: Promotional Materials
    - Posters- Red Hot + Bothered, 1995; cuid8388 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Oversize Series VIII: The Beat Experience / Offbeat: A Red Hot Soundtrip
  - Subseries B: Promotional Materials
    - Poster - Offbeat: A Red Hot Soundtrip, cuid8389 (Box [45], Folder [14])
    - Poster- The Beat Experience, [n.d]; cuid8390 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Offbeat: The Red Hot Remixes; Red Hot Organization, 1996; cuid8391 (Box 42)
    - T-Shirt: Offbeat, [n.d.]; cuid8392 (Box 33, Object ID: 191.2.0008)
- Oversize Series IX: America Is Dying Slowly
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - In-store play sampler; EastWest Records America, 1996; cuid8393 (Box 43)
    - Posters - America Is Dying Slowly, 1996; cuid8394 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings, 1995 - 1996; cuid8395
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - America Is Dying Slowly vinyl sleeve, 1996; cuid8396 (Box 43)
    - T-shirts - America Is Dying Slowly, [n.d.]; cuid8397 (Box 33, Object ID: 191.2.0009)
- Oversize Series X: Red Hot + Rio
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Press clippings, 1996; cuid8398 (Box [46])
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - T-shirt - Red Hot + Rio, [n.d.]; cuid8399 (Box 34, Object ID: 191.2.0010)
- Oversize Series XI: Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - Invoice: Scarlett Letters, 1997; cuid8400 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Press clippings, 1997; cuid8401 (Box [46])
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - T-shirt - Silencio=Muerte, [n.d.]; cuid8402 (Box 34, Object ID: 191.2.0011)
- Oversize Series XII: Every Nation (from "Diana, Princess of Wales - Tribute")
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Press clippings, 1997 - 1998; cuid8403 (Box [46])
- Oversize Series XIII: Onda Sonora: Red Hot + Lisbon, 1998 - 1999
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 1998 - 1999
    - Posters - Onda Sonora: Red Hot + Lisbon, cuid8404 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Press reviews, 1998 - 1999; cuid8405 (Box [46])
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - T-shirts - Red Hot + Lisbon, [n.d.]; cuid8406 (Box 34, Object ID: 191.2.0012)
- Oversize Series XIV: Red Hot + Rhapsody
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Poster sign - Red Hot + Rhapsody, [n.d.]; cuid8407 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings, 1998; cuid8408 (Box [46])
    - Promotional sampler: Selections from Red Hot + Rhapsody, in collaboration with Levi's; Antilles Records, 1998; cuid8409 (Box 43)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Red Hot + Rhapsody double vinyl; Verve Records, 1998; cuid8410 (Box 43)
- Oversize Series XVI: Red Hot + Indigo
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Press clippings, 2001; cuid8411 (Box [46])
- Oversize Series XVIII: Red Hot + Riot
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Posters - Red Hot + Riot, 2002; cuid8412 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Sampler featuring "Gentlemen," "Shakara/Lady" and "Zombie [Part One];" MCA Records, 2002; cuid8413 (Box 43)
    - Sampler featuring "Water No Get Enemy," "Fela Mentality" and "Shuffering + Shmiling;" MCA Records, 2002; cuid8414 (Box 43)
- Oversize Series XIX: General Red Hot Organization
  - Subseries A: Administration Files
    - Invoice: CD&L, 2000-01; cuid8415 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Subseries B: Promotional Materials
      - Posters - General, 1997-98; cuid8416 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - Press Clippings - General, 1993-98; cuid8417 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Press Clippings - 10th Anniversary - Art Forum, 2000; cuid8418 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Oversize Series XIX: General Red Hot Organization
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - Invoices: CD&L, 2000-2001; cuid8419 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Posters, 1997-1998; cuid8420 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Press clippings: General, 1993-1998; cuid8421 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Press clippings: 10th anniversary - ArtForum, November 2000; cuid8422 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - "One," U2: AIDS research benefit album featuring photograph by David Wojnarowicz on cover; Island Records, 1992; cuid8423 (Box 42)
    - T-shirt - "everybody", [n.d.]; cuid8424 (Box 34, Object ID: 191.2.0013)
    - T-shirts - Red Hot Organization contributers, c.a. 1994; cuid8425 (Box 35, Object ID: 191.2.0014)
    - T-shirt - safer sex is hot sex, female couple, [n.d.]; cuid8426 (Box 35, Object ID: 191.2.0015)
    - T-shirt - safer sex is hot sex, male couple, [n.d.]; cuid8427 (Box 35, Object ID: 191.2.0016)
- Series XXIV: Organizational Digital Data Storage
  - All of No Alt, 1996; cuid8620; SyQuest 88 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0001)
    This item has been separated from Series IIIA, Box 4, Folder 13.
  - Red Hot + Country Disk, 1994; cuid8621; SyQuest 88 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0002)
    This item has been separated from Series VA, Box 5, Folder 76.
  - Red Hot + Bothered #2 Archive, 1992-1995; cuid8622; SyQuest 88 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0003)
    This item has been separated from Series VIIA, Box 8, folder 53.
  - Red Hot + Beat, 1995; cuid8623; SyQuest 88 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0004)
    This item has been separated from Series VIIIA, Box 9, folder 36.
  - America @ (RHO #7), 1994-1996; cuid8624; SyQuest 45 MB Removable Hard Disk (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0005)
    This item has been separated from Series IXA, Box 10, folder 27.
  - Elektra, 1994-1996; cuid8625; SyQuest 45 MB Removable Hard Disk (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0006)
    This item has been separated from Series IXA, Box 11, folder 12.
  - Red Hot # 18, 1993-1996; cuid8626; SyQuest 45 MB Removable Hard Disk (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0007)
    This item has been separated from Series IXA, Box 11, folder 35.
  - Return to Helene Silverman / Final "America is Dying Slowly" Artwork, 1994-1996; cuid8627; SyQuest 45 MB Removable Hard Disk (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0008)
    This item has been separated from Series IXA, Box 11, folder 36.
  - Red Hot 16, 1993-1996; cuid8628; SyQuest 88 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0009)
    This item has been separated from Series XA, Box 12, folder 47.
  - From Movieplay, Undated; cuid8629; SyQuest 200 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0010)
    This item has been separated from Series XIXA, Box 23, folder 24.
  - Red Hot + Bothered - Important Beat Stills, 1994-1995; cuid8630; SyQuest 88 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0011)
    This item has been separated from Series XIXA, Box 28, folder 9.
  - Red Hot # 15, 1990-1996; cuid8631; SyQuest 88 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0012)
    This item has been separated from Series XIXA, Box 28, folder 10.
  - Red Hot Disk 1, 1989-1996; cuid8632; SyQuest 44 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge (Box 233, Item ID: 191.3.0013)
    This item has been separated from Series XIXA, Box 28, folder 12.